(Man:)It's unnecessarily graphic.
(Sheldon:)Hold on, Doctor.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, where are
your social skills?
(Sheldon:)This man is
clearly upset.
(Sheldon:)We should invite him
in for a hot beverage.
(Leonard:)He tried to score with Penny.
(Sheldon:)So have these two, and they're
having dinner with us.
(Amy:)So, how was
work today?
(Bernadette:)It was fine,
but you'll be happy to know
(Bernadette:)they pulled
the sexy scientists article.
(Amy:)What happened?
(Bernadette:)I don't know.
(Bernadette:)They just canceled
the photo shoot
(Bernadette:)and said they're rethinking it.
(Amy:)Well, I'm
really sorry,
(Amy:)but I think it's
for the best.
(Amy:)You want people focusing
on your achievements,
(Amy:)not staring at your
breasts in some magazine.
(Bernadette:)I guess.
(Bernadette:)It's really not that important.
(Bernadette:)Hey, up here.
Sorry, we're...
we were talking about them.